<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Tekeoglan&#39;s Blog</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
        <description>Recent content on Tekeoglan&#39;s Blog</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <copyright>tekeoglan</copyright>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Archives</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/archives/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/archives/</guid>
        <description></description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>About Me</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/about-me/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/about-me/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hey there, I’m a 31-year-old programmer living in Türkiye, and my story&amp;rsquo;s had some pretty sharp turns. If you ever felt like you&amp;rsquo;re always searching for your thing, trust me, you&amp;rsquo;re not alone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve always been that kid who loved computers and math. School? Not really my jam. Except for math class and drawing—those were my safe zones. But when it came time for college, my dad pushed me into Construction Engineering. Spoiler: I hated it. The lectures dragged, depression hit hard, and eventually I dropped out. That whole period? A blur of confusion, games, and existential dread.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking of games, I played &lt;em&gt;a lot&lt;/em&gt;. But somewhere in the middle of grinding XP and building virtual worlds, I thought, &amp;ldquo;Wait&amp;hellip; what if I made my own game?&amp;rdquo; That spark led me to programming. It felt like unlocking developer mode in life—suddenly I had access to the code behind the curtains. I dived in, taught myself how to program, and it actually made sense. I loved writing the logic and constructing the systems. But animating characters and designing assets? Not for me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So I pivoted—hello, web development. Except I fell into the rabbit hole of &amp;ldquo;Which framework should I learn? React or Svelte? Which language should I learn? Go or JavaScript?&amp;rdquo; And somewhere in that mess, I got lost again. I kept jumping from one tool or language to the next, burning out the second something lost its novelty. Eventually, I asked myself: why do I keep doing this?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Turns out, ADHD was the missing puzzle piece. Got diagnosed, started meds, and slowly things started clicking into place. Depression lifted. Focus improved. Now I’m rebuilding from the ground up—studying math again, solving problems, diving into algorithms, and finally feeling like I’m making steady progress.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These days, I’m a mix of a tinker and a thinker. I love building stuff, breaking it, and putting it back together just to see how it works. I’m into Linux (currently rocking Fedora with Hyprland), and my terminal setup is basically a handcrafted digital cockpit. I code mostly in Go and JavaScript, and I live in Neovim like it’s my command center.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I&amp;rsquo;m not coding, I’m probably reading something deep on philosophy, psychology, or history. I’m also fascinated by physics and the way the universe operates—the fundamental laws, the chaos and beauty of the cosmos.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I cook too—because honestly, writing a good recipe feels a lot like writing a clean function: clear inputs, a logical process, and a delicious output. Music is always playing in the background of my life, too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I use Obsidian and Zotero for notes—they’re my second brain. And while I still explore new ideas like Linux ricing, advanced math, side projects, I’m starting to learn how to stick with things and go deeper.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So yeah, I’m a curious mind, always learning, always wandering.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Search</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/search/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/search/</guid>
        <description></description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
